Narrator: 1
A: This is for my foodie friends.
In case you thought lettuce was only for salads,
here I’m cooking it in some butter with an onion.
Then I add some mushrooms, chicken, fresh tomatoes,
and some other things – not sure yet.
Lettuce is also great in soups, or you can grill it and serve it with blue cheese.
Narrator: 2
B: We didn’t feel like cooking last night, and besides,
we didn’t have any food in the house,
so we decided to order some take-out salads from our wonderful local pizzeria.
They were all very good, but my favorite was a chicken salad
with carrots, tomatoes, peppers, lettuce, and some pieces of fried bread.
Narrator: 3
C: Brunch, Sunday afternoon, at a restaurant in the East Village, called Timna.
We had lots of different sharing plates.
I loved everything, especially this dish called shakshuka, which is North African,
and it’s basically eggs in a tomato sauce,
but the mixture of herbs and spices makes it taste great.
And the bread we had to dip in the sauce was wonderful, too.
Go there. Soon.
Narrator: 4
D: OK, guys, this is it!
Our Thanksgiving dinner – which we had at 6:30 last night.
All the usual things: turkey with cranberry sauce, mashed potatoes,
sweet potatoes, lots of vegetables, and more… and more…
We thought about going to a restaurant this year, maybe having seafood,
but then we decided, no, we like homemade and traditional,
so we stayed at home and cooked together.
I now need to spend a few hours on the sofa before I even think of going to bed.
So, how was yours?